

## **Profile**

I'm a passionate and motivated programmer with a lot of experience working with data. My formal undergraduate studies in Economics, Philosophy and Electrical Engineering reflect my broad interest in a wide range of academic areas – both in the humanities and STEM – and have provided a foundation for my passion for self-learning.

# **Employment History**

## PhD Candidate, Monash Univerity, Melbourne

OCTOBER 2018 - PRESENT

- Developing Deep Learning based algorithms in Python to improve generalisation of Artificial Intelligence agents to unseen and/or varying environments
- Worked extensively with PyTorch, Numpy, Linux and Git

#### Teaching Associate, Monash University, Melbourne

MARCH 2019 - NOVEMBER 2021

 Facilitating classes and teaching content for fourth year Computer Vision (ECE4076) and first year electronics (ENG1002)

#### Research Assistant, QuantEcon (https://quantecon.org/), Canberra

APRIL 2017 - DECEMBER 2021

- Maintaining and debugging Python and Julia code for the QuantEcon learning content, using test-driven development
- Contributing to new content, including interactive Jupyter notebooks

#### Technical Services Analyst, Experian Asia Pacific, Melbourne

DECEMBER 2015 - FEBRUARY 2017

- Automating internal data processing with Python and SQL
- Running targeted Facebook ads with A/B testing to measure impact
- Building programs using Python, SQL and the Facebook SDK to assist the sales team

## Education

#### Graduate Diploma of Economics, Australian National University, Canberra

FEBRUARY 2017 - NOVEMBER 2017

WAM 80.25

# Bachelor of Engineering with Honours and Bachelor of Arts, Monash University, Melbourne

FEBRUARY 2010 - NOVEMBER 2015

WAM 73.2

# **Qualifications**

Microsoft Azure DP-900

**Details** 

Elsternwick 3185, Melbourne Australia 0412956747

ajhebblewhite@gmail.com

Links

LinkedIn

Website

Skills

Python

Machine Learning

Data Analysis

SQL

JavaScript

Web Development

Econometrics

202

# **Informal Education**

Microsoft Azure Data Engineering Associate DP-203 Exam Prep Specialization, Coursera

2021

The Complete 2021 Web Development Bootcamp, Udemy

2021

Practical Reinforcement Learning, National Research University, Coursera

2018

Bayesian Methods for Hackers (JuPyter Notebook Course), https://github.com/CamDavidsonPilon/Probabilistic-Programming-and-Bayesian-Methods-for-Hackers

Intro to Machine Learning, Udacity

2016

Neural Networks for Machie Learning, University of Toronto Coursera

2015

## References

References available upon request